Guide to the Don Brockett Papers, 1930-1998 CTC.2002.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Don Brockett Papers
1930-1998
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Brockett, Don
CTC.2002.01
15 Linear Feet (36 boxes)
The Don Brockett Papers contain scrapbooks, photographs, contracts, correspondence, and other types of materials relating to the stage productions from the career of entertainer, television, and film personality Don Brockett of Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
Previous Citation
Don Brockett Papers, 1930-1995, CTC.2002.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
Don Brockett Papers, 1930-1995, CTC.32, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
Materials in the Brockett Papers date from his early years as an entertainer from the 1950s through 1995. This collection includes all types of materials, such as photographs, posters, scripts, scores, orchestrations, press clippings, programs, and other promotional materials. Also included are a sampling of Brockett's business contracts, copyrights, and correspondence with various friends, other entertainers, and booking agents.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Biography
Don Brockett was born in 1930 and lived in and around Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, throughout his life. He produced, directed, wrote, composed, and usually performed in most of his own shows from the late 1950s until his sudden death in 1995. During his stage career, he also simultaneously managed several other entertainment acts such as Jack and Sally Jenkins and the popular Turtle Creek band, The Vogues. Mr. Brockett was nationally known due to his portrayal of Chef Brockett on the PBS children's education series Mr. Roger's Neighborhood for over thirty years.
What truly made Don Brockett unique were his stage productions performed in and around the city of Pittsburgh. Most of these productions also toured in neighboring states and several were performed throughout the country and Off-Broadway in New York City. A large number of his early shows were created for the duo of Brockett and Barbara Mazziotti, (later Russell), who performed musical revues to critical and commercial praise. In 1985 he premiered Forbidden Pittsburgh, which became a celebrated event that would run annually for the next decade. The show featured popular Broadway songs customized to poke fun at local topics, trends, and personalities. He once estimated that he had employed over one thousand Pittsburgh entertainers throughout his career, several of which went on to greater fame like Florence Lacy, Beth Austin, Lenora Nemetz, Rob Marshall, Pam Klinger, and Michael Keaton.
Later in Don Brockett's career, he began to acquire supporting roles in film. He appeared in thirty-five films, many of which were filmed in the Pittsburgh area. His first film was Flashdance (1983). He then went on to appear in other major motion pictures, such as Fletch Lives with Chevy Chase and Hoffa with Jack Nicholson and Danny Devito. He also had a small role in the Academy Award winner for Best Picture of 1991, The Silence of the Lambs.
Arrangement
Series I. Personal Materials
Series II. Legal and Financial Materials
Series III. Career Related Materials
Series IV. Brockett Productions
Series V. Orchestrations
Series VI. Photographs
Series VII. Oversized and Miscellaneous Materials
Acquisition Information
Gift of Leslie Brockett in April 2002.
Pittsburgh (Pa.); Burlesque (Theater) -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Musical theater producers and directors -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Actors and actresses -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Musical theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Mister Rogers' neighborhood (Television program); Theatrical companies -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Performing arts -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Entertainers -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Theater; Brockett, Don
- Personal Materials, 1947-1991; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series contains a small amount of personal effects and other items. The awards that Brockett received include letters of acknowledgement from U.S. Senator John Heinz, and both the Senate and House of Representatives of Pennsylvania. The notebooks and journals contain Brockett's notes, thoughts, and experiences during the planning of the Off-Broadway debut of Big Bad Burlesque.
  - Awards, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - St. Mary of the Mount High School yearbook - graduating year, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Big Bad Burlesque notebook/journal (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Legal and Financial Materials, 1963-1994; II.
  This series contains a small amount of various formal legal documents and materials.
  - Copyrights, 1963-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Contracts, 1985-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Expenses while employed by T.V. Guide, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Writer/Publishers Clearance Forms, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Career Related Materials, 1943-1998; III.
  Items in this series relate to Brockett's career in general and not to any one specific production. Contained within are histories, correspondence, television and film scripts, and newsclippings, some of which were arranged into various scrapbooks. Some of the scrapbooks have been preservation photocopied; these copies are housed in the same folder as the original materials.
  - Brockett and Barbara promotional materials, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chronology and history of Brockett productions, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1992 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Phyllis Diller, 1964-1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Don Brockett's Pittsburgh - the Video, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous film and television scripts - Brockett scenes only, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous promotional materials, 1964-1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 2-5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1981-1995 (Box 4, Folder 8-16)
  - Newspaper clippings - undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook loose pages 1-96, 1943-1970 (Box 5, Folder 1-10)
  - Scrapbook - fragments, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Script - Flashdance, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Script - Fletch II, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Script - The Nobodies television pilot, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Script - Picking Up the Pieces, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Stouffer's Lean Cuisine jingle lyrics, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Brockett Productions, 1962-1994; IV.
  This series contains materials that relate to specific productions of Brockett's. It is divided into three subseries: Scripts, Scores, and Skits / Other materials.
  - Scripts, 1969-1994; 1.
    Boxes 8-14 are production scripts to many of Brockett's shows, which are arranged alphabetically by title. For some titles the folder not only contains the script, but also other items that pertain to the production, such as music orchestrations and correspondence.
    - Amen, Amen Etc. script (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Beads script, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Bicentennial Wagon Train Show script, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Big Bad Burlesque script - Orpheum Theatre / office copy (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Big Bad Burlesque script - lighting cues for club date version (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Big Bad Burlesque script - revised, November 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Big Bad Burlesque script - office copy, April 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Bless My Soul script (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Bring on the Broads script, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Broadway Big Top (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Broadway Tonight - Heinz Hall, November 12 1971 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Brockett and Barbara and Friends - Marriott, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Brockett and Barbara in Trashdance, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Brockett and Barbara at 104 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Brockett and Barbara in Sixtysomething (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Brockett and Barbara's 25th Anniversary (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Burlesqapade - copies of scripts (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
    - Burlesque Gaieties script, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Cat Cay, March 10 1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Celebration '76 script and promotional materials, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Commercials scripts (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Cowardly Way Out script (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
    - Desdamona Fink Meets Son of Stage Struck (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Don Brockett with Champagne (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Don't Feed the Crockagators script, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Don Brockett's Forbidden Pittsburgh '85 script - original office copy (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Don Brockett's Forbidden Pittsburgh '86 script, April 1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Don Brockett's Forbidden Pittsburgh '86 script - office copy (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Don Brockett's Forbidden Pittsburgh '87 script (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Don Brockett's Forbidden Pittsburgh '88 script (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Don Brockett's Forbidden Pittsburgh '89 script (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Don Brockett's Forbidden Pittsburgh '90 script, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
    - Don Brockett's Forbidden Pittsburgh '92 script, July 1992 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Don Brockett's Forbidden Pittsburgh '93 script, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Don Brockett's Forbidden Pittsburgh '94 script (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Don Brockett's Forbidden Pittsburgh '95 script (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Fred Rogers 25th anniversary special script, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
    - Gimbels Bunny Breakfast script, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Gimbels Christmas show script, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Go Pound Salt script - Ben Gross restaurant, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
    - Hello Tourists script (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - How the West was Won script, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
    - Industrial Show script and promotional materials (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Ingersoll Rand script - office copy with final changes (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Josephine the Short Neck Giraffe the sequel! script, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Loveboat Follies script (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Love Song script (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - Lyrics Verse script (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - National Jewish Test script (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - New Amen Show script - Baltimore (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - New Amen Show script - Marriott (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - New Amen Show script with changes, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - NYC Update script (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Peaches and Bananas script, July 1 1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Peaches and Bananas script office copy and score, July 1 1980 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania Show script, November 17 1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Politics '72 script - Ben Gross restaurant, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Poor Pitiful Pittsburgh script - Ben Gross Restaurant, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Places Please script (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Places Please script office copy (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Pretty Please script (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Riverboat Follies, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Santa's Workshop script, October 25 1984 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Sights and Sounds of Pittsburgh script, November 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Son of Stage Struck script (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Stage Struck script (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
    - Sweet Feet script (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Sweet Feet - Cockeysville, May 1974 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Sweet Feet script - Jennerstown Baltimore re-write (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Symphony Cabaret script - Duquesne Club, April 4 1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Tom Smith script, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - TV or Not TV script - Celestial, March 11 1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - U.J.F. Show Full of Life, October 1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Vintage Brockett and Barbara script, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Vintage Brockett and Barbara Again script, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Wake Up Santa (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Who Needs a Showtrain? script and early music and sketches (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - You Get Your Show script, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Scores, 1969-1994; 2.
    Boxes 15-17 contain the production scores to several of Brockett's shows; they are arranged alphabetically by the title of the production.
    - Amen, Amen, Etc. score, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    - Big Bad Burlesque full score, January 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Big Bad Burlesque score (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
    - Big Bad Burlesque score (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Big Bad Burlesque piano score, January 1982 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Big Bad Burlesque - Burlesque Gaieties score (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Bless My Soul score (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Forbidden Pittsburgh '85 score (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Forbidden Pittsburgh '93 score (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Forbidden Pittsburgh '94 score, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Industrial Show music, 1969-1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Ingersol Rand score, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Just for Openers score (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Mister Roger's Operas, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - The New Amen Show score (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Not Tonight I Have a Headache score (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Sweet Feet score, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 8-10)
    - Utopia 20 score, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified scores (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Skits and other materials, 1962-1978; 3.
    Boxes 18 and 19 are an alphabetical arrangement by title prepared by Don Brockett of skits, comedic scenes, intros, medleys, and some lyrics to songs. Box 20 consists of miscellaneous materials including scrapbooks, programs, artwork, etc.
    - Skits, intros, lyrics, etc "A-M" (Box 18, Folder 1-10)
    - Skits, intros, lyrics, etc "N-Z" (Box 19, Folder 1-7)
    - Big Bad Burlesque scrapbook (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Brockett's Broadway Babes planning (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Fred Rogers 25th anniversary special planning (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Industrial Show programs (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous artwork (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - N.Y.C. stage manager's book (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Peaches and Bananas artwork (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Programs, 1968-1993 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Special Material (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Tony Domino finale - rough draft (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Orchestrations, V.
  Within this series are song orchestrations that were used by Brockett for his multitude of stage productions. They are arranged into four subseries: Known composers, Brockett composed, Unknown composers, and Other orchestrations.
  - Known Composers, 1.
    Box 21 contains orchestrations by composers who are not Don Brockett and are clearly identified on the materials; they are arranged alphabetically by the song title.
    - Ac-cent-tchu-aate the Positive (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Almawhatsamater (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - And All that Jazz (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - And I'm Telling You I'm Not Going (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Before the Parade Passes By (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Can-Can (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Hawaiian War Chant (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Hello My Baby (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - The Impossible Dream (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - It's You I Like (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Louise (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Men in My Little Girl's Life (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Mimi (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Mr. Whipple's Watching (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Night Fever (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Oh! You Beautiful Doll (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Rocky theme (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Swan Lake Ballet Suite (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Teen Angel (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Thank Heaven for Little Girls (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Thanks to You (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Tomorrow (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Union Label (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - We Didn't Start the Fire (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Welcome to Brockett's Revue (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - What I Did For Love (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Wilkommen (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Wonderful Night (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - You Made Me Love You (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Brockett Composed, 2.
    Box 22 contains orchestrations labeled as being composed by Don Brockett; they are arranged alphabetically by the title of the piece.
    - Airport Polka (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - All We Know is That She's Here (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Bi-Centennial Production (community theatre) (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Big Old Lady (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Capital B (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Casey and Kildare (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Chickenanny (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Dirty Old Lady (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Fight Song (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - How Do You Like It So Far? (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - I Can't Remember Her Name (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - If That is the Kind of Woman He Wants (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - I Want Me a Woman (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Jumbo (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Kuelling (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Last Night I Met Miss Right, Mom (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Last Polka in Pittsburgh (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Lord Sees Me (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Love Songs (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - My Christmas Wish (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - My Darling When You Go Away (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Nikita Cha-Cha (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Nose Touching Song (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Old Fashioned Good Night (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Old Prayer in a New Song (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Places Please (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Pretty Things (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Rich Kid, Poor Kid (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Santa (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Santa Claus Blues (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Sea Captain's Daughter (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Sinatra Records (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Sing a Song (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Song of Love (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Stage Struck (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Subway (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Sweet Feet (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Tango de March (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - To the Dentist (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Two of Us (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Wake Up Santa (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - We're Both Twelve Now (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Who Needs a Showtrain? (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Who Will Finish the Season? (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Wonderful Burlesque Days (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - You Can't Poke Fun at the Palace (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Unknown Composers, 3.
    Boxes 23-28 are orchestrations composed by miscellaneous composers (some of which are possibly Brockett and some that are popular famous composers) but the composer is not specifically identified on the materials; they are arranged alphabetically by the title of the piece.
    - A.M. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Acts (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Ah Paris (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - All of Me (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Amen (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Amen Commercials (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Anything Goes (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Application (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Applause (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Arnie Palmer (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Avon Beguine (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Back Home in Indiana (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Balloon (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Battle Hymn (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Big Bad Burlesque Bows (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Big Bad Burlesque Opening (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Big Spender (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Bill (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Bill Bailey (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - The Birth of the Blues (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Bonnie and Clyde (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Boompies (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Broadway Tonight (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Brockett and Barbara Under Broadway (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Brockett's Big Bad Burlesque (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Brockett Opening Number (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Brotherhood (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Bug Production (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Burlesque (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Burlesque Overture (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Cabaret (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Can I Take You Home (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Carioca (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Chair Commercial Chaser (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Chef Brockett Song (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Ching and Ling (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Christmas Wish (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Cinderella (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Clairol-Opener (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Clyde and Hortense (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Comatose or Death (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Commercials (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Community Songs (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - The Company Way (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Diet Coke (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Dis-Done (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Doctor and the Lady (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Downtown (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Dry Bones (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Easy Credit (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Eat n Park (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Elf March (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Entertain (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Everybody's Fancy (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Fiddler (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - The First Time You Notice (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Football Production (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Five Growing Boys (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - 42nd Street (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Funs a Poppin' (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Gas: It's Quite an Art (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Give My Regards to Broadway (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Glamour Girl (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Gunner (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Happy Days are Here Again (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Hard Time to Come Again No More (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Hats Off to Broadway (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Hello Dolly (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Here is Your Tent (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Home Show (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - I am Taking Pictures (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - I Can't Apologize Enough (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - I Could Have Danced All Night (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - I Dig Rock and Roll Music (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - I Don't Know how to Love Him (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - If I Were a Rich Man (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - If Only Moderately (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - If We Only Have Love (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - I Just Can't Wait (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Improvisations Chaser (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Inkka-dink-ka-dink (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Intro to BQ Days (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - I Really Love it Up Here (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - I Remember it Well (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - I Ride My Horse (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - It's Quite an Act (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Jim and Tammy (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - John Wayne (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - K-I-D-S (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Lakeview Sheraton (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Lee Norse Commercial Jingle (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Let Us Entertain You (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Little Do They Know (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Little Rock (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Lizzie Borden (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Long Way to September (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Lord Be With You (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Lullaby of Broadway (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Mame (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Mary Poppins (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Maybe (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - May Best (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Meet the Champion (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Miss America (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Mistaken Identity (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Mr. Foo (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Mr. Goldberg (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - My Heart Belongs to Daddy (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Nepitism (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - New Amen Show Opening (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - New York, New York (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - New York Chaser (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - New York Opening (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Nights on Broadway (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - The Nobodies (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Numero Uno (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Oh You Can't Fly to Heaven (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Old Folks at Home (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Old Song (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Opening Talk (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Ooh My Feet (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Opera (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Orphan Annie (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Orphan Dolls (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Patriotic Production (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Paper Production (Box 27, Folder 13)